gadgetdiary.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

Thankyou our visitor to stay in touch with us and spread the word. The privacy policy is about, how we collect your information, use it and secure your personal information from the outer world. Privacy is what we all need in this online environment because this world is not secure, but at http://gadgetdiary.com, we respect that you share your private information with us and we will make our best efforts to protect your privacy.

So you can freely share your experience and thoughts with us without annoying of your personal data being shared here.

 **Notice** : ( what we collect?)

We collect your information like your name, identity, your email id, in any case we will not sell or rent this information to anyone.  We will use your information only to respond you, regarding the reason you contacted us or shared your thoughts with us.

 **Cookies**

Cookies help us to find which pages you find really useful and which not. It is surely a better way to monitor and track what you like to see. Many of the third party advertiser use cookies to serve ads to site to measure advertisement effectiveness and some use cookies for other reasons. Cookies can also be deleted from your computer as soon as you close your browser.

 **Security**

We take precautions to protect your information; we are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable, physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy without any prior notice.

 _If you have any questions regarding this policy please feel free to_ _contact us_ _any time_
